celeb-ads.com 2016-04-04

# Celeb Ad - Privacy Policy

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, and protect your personal information. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our Service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with 30 days' prior notice by posting notice of the change on the Celeb Ad website.

Throughout this policy, we use the term "Personal Information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user.

1\. Personal Information Collection

1.1. When you visit the Celeb Ad website, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website.

1.2. If you open an account, we collect the following types of information from you:

Contact information: your name, address, phone, email, instant messenger ID, and other similar information.

Financial information: the full bank account numbers and credit card numbers that you link to your Celeb Ad account.

1.3. Before permitting you to use our Service, we may require you to provide additional information we can use to verify your identity or address or manage risk, such as your date of birth, passport, or other information. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services.

1.4. When you are using our Service, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

1.5. Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

2\. Cookies

2.1. When you access our website, we, or companies we hire to track how our website is used, may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer.

2.2. We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session so that we don't need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.

2.3. We also use longer-lasting cookies for other purposes such as to display your email address on our sign-in form so that you don't need to retype the email address each time you log in to your account.

2.4. We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website. We may also collect information about your computer or other access device to mitigate risk and for fraud prevention purposes.

3\. Personal Information Protection

3.1. We store and process your personal information on extremely secured dedicated servers, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable government regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfil their job responsibilities.

4\. Use of Personal Information

4.1. Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

provide the services and customer support you request;

process transactions and send notices about your transactions;

resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service;

customize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website;

send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;

compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.
